qzzr.com 2016-05-29

# Privacy Policy | Qzzr

## Qzzr / Movement Ventures Privacy Policy

This is a privacy policy provided by the folks at [Movement Ventures](http://movementventures.com/) (who created Qzzr.com – “Qzzr”) when you use the [Qzzr site](http://qzzr.com/) and the services and products found there.

Your privacy is critically important to us. At Movement we have a few fundamental principles:

  *  __

We don’t ask you for personal information unless we truly need it. (We can’t stand services that ask you for things like your gender or income level for no apparent reason.)

  *  __

We don’t share your personal information with anyone except to comply with the law, develop our products, or protect our rights.

  *  __

We don’t store personal information on our servers unless required for the on-going operation of one of our services.

  *  __

In our products, we aim to make it as simple as possible for you to control what’s visible to the public, seen by search engines, kept private, and permanently deleted.

  *  __

If you have questions about deleting or correcting your personal data please contact our support team.

### Site Visitors

Like most site operators, Movement collects non-personally-identifying information of the sort that web browsers and servers typically make available, such as the browser type, language preference, referring site, and the date and time of each visitor request. Movement’s purpose in collecting non-personally identifying information is to better understand how Movement’s visitors use its website. From time to time, Movement may release non-personally-identifying information in the aggregate, e.g., by publishing a report on trends in the usage of its website.

Movement also collects potentially personally-identifying information like Internet Protocol (IP) addresses. Movement only discloses logged in user and commenter IP addresses under the same circumstances that it uses and discloses personally-identifying information as described below.

### Gathering of Personally-Identifying Information

Certain visitors to Movement’s websites choose to interact with Movement in ways that require Movement to gather personally-identifying information. The amount and type of information that Movement gathers depends on the nature of the interaction. In each case, Movement collects such information only as is necessary or appropriate to fulfill the purpose of the visitor’s interaction with Movement. Movement does not disclose personally-identifying information other than as described below. And visitors can always refuse to supply personally-identifying information, with the caveat that it may prevent them from engaging in certain website-related activities.

### Aggregated Statistics

Movement may collect statistics about the behavior of visitors to its websites. Movement may display this information publicly or provide it to others. However, Movement does not disclose personally-identifying information other than as described below.

### Protection of Certain Personally-Identifying Information

Movement discloses potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information only to those of its employees, contractors and affiliated organizations that (i) need to know that information in order to process it on Movement’s behalf or to provide services available at Movement’s websites, and (ii) that have agreed not to disclose it to others. Some of those employees, contractors and affiliated organizations may be located outside of your home country; by using Movement’s websites, you consent to the transfer of such information to them. Movement will not rent or sell potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information to anyone. Other than to its employees, contractors and affiliated organizations, as described above, Movement discloses potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information only in response to a subpoena, court order or other governmental request, or when Movement believes in good faith that disclosure is reasonably necessary to protect the property or rights of Movement, third parties or the public at large. If you are a registered user of a Movement website and have supplied your email address, Movement may occasionally send you an email to tell you about new features, solicit your feedback, or just keep you up to date with what’s going on with Movement and our products. We primarily use our various product blogs to communicate this type of information, so we expect to keep this type of email to a minimum. If you send us a request (for example via a support email or via one of our feedback mechanisms), we reserve the right to publish it in order to help us clarify or respond to your request or to help us support other users. Movement takes all measures reasonably necessary to protect against the unauthorized access, use, alteration or destruction of potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information.

### Payment Information

Movement uses secure services for online card payment transactions and does not record or store credit card information on its Site or servers.

### Cookies

A cookie is a string of information that a website stores on a visitor’s computer, and that the visitor’s browser provides to the website each time the visitor returns. Movement uses cookies to help Movement identify and track visitors, their usage of the Movement website, and their website access preferences. Movement visitors who do not wish to have cookies placed on their computers should set their browsers to refuse cookies before using Movement’s websites, with the drawback that certain features of Movement’s websites may not function properly without the aid of cookies.

Movement also uses a first-party Google Analytics cookie in order to track usage of Movement’s websites and to provide a more relevant experience to our users. Visitors can opt out of the Google Analytics features by using the Google Analytics Opt-out Browser Add-on available [here.](https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout/)

### Business Transfers

If Movement, or its assets, were acquired, or in the unlikely event that Movement goes out of business or enters bankruptcy, user information would be one of the assets that is transferred or acquired by a third party. You acknowledge that such transfers may occur, and that any acquirer of Movement may continue to use your personal information as set forth in this policy.

### Privacy Policy Changes

Although most changes are likely to be minor, Movement may change its Privacy Policy from time to time, and in Movement’s sole discretion. Movement encourages visitors to frequently check this page for any changes to its Privacy Policy. Your continued use of any of Movement’s sites after any change in this Privacy Policy will constitute your acceptance of such change.

This privacy policy was last modified on 8/27/14.

  *  __

 **8/27/14: Added paragraph about Google Analytics Cookies:** Movement also uses a first-party Google Analytics cookie in order to track usage of Movement’s websites and to provide a more relevant experience to our users. Visitors can opt out of the Google Analytics features by using the Google Analytics Opt-out Browser Add-on available [here.](https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout/)
